Longman Activator 2nd Ed. (En-En).

This dictionary takes you from a key word or basic idea, such as 'good',
and shows you more related words or phrases with information on register,
context and grammar structures.

    * Detailed definitions help users choose the correct word.
    * Natural, corpus-based examples show words in typical usage.
    * Improved access system makes it easy to find the word you need.
    * All the collocations and phrases you need to write correctly.
    * Clear key words help to find alternatives.
    * Concepts are grouped.
    * Simple definitions an examples help to find the right word.

Source:
Longman Dictionary of Contemporary English DVD, 5th Ed.

Headwords/Entries: 19263/18700

Version: 2.1 (16 May 2009)

Changes: Fixed some broken (in the original software!) transcriptions.
