Longman Dictionary of Contemporary English 5th Ed.

This new edition of "The Longman Dictionary of Contempory English"
is the most comprehensive learner's dictionary ever.

It includes:
 * 230,000 words, phrases and meanings – more than
   any other advanced learner’s dictionary.
 * 165,000 examples
 * Clear definitions written using only 2,000 common words.
 * Over 18,000 synonyms, antonyms and related words.
 * Over 65,000 collocations.
 * Over 1,200 pictures.
 * NEW 88,000 spoken example sentences pronounced.
 * NEW Integrated Collocations Dictionary. Over 65,000
   collocations will improve students' fluency.
 * NEW Integrated Thesaurus. Over 18,000 synonyms, antonyms
   and related words will improve vocabulary range.
 * NEW Register Notes focus on the differences between
   spoken and written English.
 * The top 3,000 most frequent words in spoken and
   written English are highlighted.
 * Academic Word List highlighted.
 * Grammar and warning notes ensure that students avoid common errors.

Source:
Longman Dictionary of Contemporary English DVD, 5th Ed.

Headwords/Entries: 62964/61212

Version: 1.0 (03 June 2009)
