Cambridge Advanced Learners Dictionary 3th Ed.

Headers: 65220
Entries: 52486
Merged: 1075
CrossRefs: 11389

Clear definitions and prominent guidewords help you find the meaning you want quickly and easily. Hundreds of new words ensure your English is up to date. And 'Word partner' boxes show you how to use words in the most natural way. * NEW! 'Extra help' section includes maps, illustrations and photos, and the innovative 'Let's Talk' section which focuses specifically on spoken English. * NEW! Even more 'Common mistakes' boxes help you avoid typical errors. * NEW! Thesaurus panels help you widen your vocabulary. The version with CD-ROM includes: * Recordings of every word in British and American English - letting you practise your pronunciation. * Interactive exercises including exam practice and past papers for IELTS, FCE, CAE, CPE and BEC. * Extra collocation information and thousands of example sentences. * UNIQUE! Cambridge SMART thesaurus turns the dictionary into a thesaurus.


# Paperback: 1814 pages
# Publisher: Cambridge University Press; 3 edition (August 11, 2008)
# Language: English
# ISBN-10: 0521712661
# ISBN-13: 978-0521712668