Merriam-Webster's Advanced Learner's Dictionary

It's here! The first learner's dictionary from America's language experts is the perfect resource for teachers and students of English as a second language, with over 100,000 words and phrases, and the most example sentences of any learner's dictionary.

Source:
http://www.learnersdictionary.com/

Headwords/Entries: 51699/51699

Version: 1.0 (August 2010)
